[
  {
    "question": "a의 발음은?",
    "correct": "에이"
  },
  {
    "question": "b의 발음은?",
    "correct": "비"
  },
  {
    "question": "c의 발음은?",
    "correct": "씨"
  },
  {
    "question": "d의 발음은?",
    "correct": "디"
  },
  {
    "question": "e의 발음은?",
    "correct": "이"
  },
  {
    "question": "f의 발음은?",
    "correct": "에프"
  },
  {
    "question": "g의 발음은?",
    "correct": "지(쥐)"
  },
  {
    "question": "h의 발음은?",
    "correct": "에이치"
  },
  {
    "question": "i의 발음은?",
    "correct": "아이"
  },
  {
    "question": "j의 발음은?",
    "correct": "제이"
  },
  {
    "question": "k의 발음은?",
    "correct": "케이"
  },
  {
    "question": "l의 발음은?",
    "correct": "엘"
  },
  {
    "question": "m의 발음은?",
    "correct": "엠"
  },
  {
    "question": "n의 발음은?",
    "correct": "엔"
  },
  {
    "question": "o의 발음은?",
    "correct": "오"
  },
  {
    "question": "p의 발음은?",
    "correct": "피"
  },
  {
    "question": "q의 발음은?",
    "correct": "큐"
  },
  {
    "question": "r의 발음은?",
    "correct": "알"
  },
  {
    "question": "s의 발음은?",
    "correct": "에스"
  },
  {
    "question": "t의 발음은?",
    "correct": "티"
  },
  {
    "question": "u의 발음은?",
    "correct": "유"
  },
  {
    "question": "v의 발음은?",
    "correct": "브이"
  },
  {
    "question": "w의 발음은?",
    "correct": "더블유"
  },
  {
    "question": "x의 발음은?",
    "correct": "엑스"
  },
  {
    "question": "y의 발음은?",
    "correct": "와이"
  },
  {
    "question": "z의 발음은?",
    "correct": "지(제트)"
  }
]
